Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
She was taking
pictures at the border.
Journalist?
No... Tourist.
Take care of it.
Please. Grant me mercy
and I will pray for the
success of your cause.
Ladies and gentlemen. what
you're about to witness
is the next evolution
in military engagement.
A machine that operates
with surgical precision.
And in a world
where every action
is under the media microscope.
this technology will
allow our nation
and its allies the means
to act quickly. decisively
and without the specter
of political blowback.
Madam Secretary. glad
you could join us.
Would you mind explaining
to me why you're conducting
a joint military operation
without my approval?
I appreciate it looks
like that. Shelly.
but we're here strictly
as technical support.
The mission's being conducted
by Saudi intelligence.
We're merely loaning
out the asset.
What are you talking
about? What asset?
Eyes are up.
You shoot me - we both die!
Naveen Tripathi. Where is he?
He's here. I can
take you to him.
What you just saw
was not only a test
of our technological prowess
but a clear message
to our enemies.
If the 21st century
wants another arms race.
you better goddamn believe
we intend to win it.
What the hell was that?
She just shot Tripathi.
-Someone get her on the comms.
-She's not responding.
What the hell is going on.
Sattler? Are we being hacked?
Everybody. stay calm! Okay?
One of you. shut this down.
We can't. We don't have control.
Well. then who the hell does?
Jesus.
You are in violation
of your orders. Amelia.
Confirm your objective.
But that would
spoil the surprise.
Before we start.
I want you to know that
nothing you say here
will get your aunt
in any trouble.
I'm no longer here by
order of the court.
I just wanted to check in
and see how you're doing.
given everything
that's happened.
I mean...
I guess it could've
been a lot worse.
A live launch for a new toy
has devolved into a
murderous rampage.
Toy designer Gemma
Forrester appeared
in a Seattle
district court today
facing charges of
reckless endangerment.
A lot of people blame
Gemma for what M3gan did.
For a long time.
she blamed herself.
But the more she went on TV
to talk about what happened.
the more she realized
she had an opportunity
to turn it into
something positive.
This is about a world in crisis.
Outsourcing our parental
duties to devices.
plowing our kids' minds
with electronically
charged dopamine hits.
You wouldn't give
your child cocaine.
Why would you give
them a smartphone?
And that's how
she met Christian.
-Hi. Gemma? Hi.
-Yeah?
Uh. Christian Bradley.
He runs a foundation
that warns people
about the dangers of AI.
They try to convince
politicians here
and around the world to
make safer laws around it
so that what happened with
M3gan doesn't happen again.
Gemma still believes technology
can be used for good.
Just that kids shouldn't
spend so much time around it.
But she always makes a point
of explaining the reasons why.
"And so. as it turned
out. companies were
"using Section 230 as
a way to skirt the law
"and monetize the
attention of children
with no regard for
their mental health."
And how do you
feel about that?
I think not being on
a device frees you up
to try other things.
Helps you make new friends.
Thanks to your dork mom.
we just had our phones
taken off of us.
Guess I'll have to find
other ways to amuse myself.
And you know what else?
You're not gonna
have that weird.
janky doll to protect you.
I guess you're right.
But let me ask you
this. Sapphire.
Who's protecting you?
Oh. so you think you're tough?
I sent you to
aikido because it is
the least aggressive
form of martial arts.
And we've talked
about the merits
of using Steven Seagal
as a role model.
I'm not saying we don't
have our problems.
but the important thing
is that we get
through them together.
Just like we said we would.
So. after what
happened with M3gan.
our team went through something
of a philosophical shift.
And while Gemma has
obviously become
a strong voice for regulation.
our company is still very
much focused on innovation
but with a specific view toward
socially conscious products
that move humanity in
the right direction.
So. with that in mind.
I'd like to present to you
our flagship invention.
The Exoskeletor Model 1.
-Cole. this is Niles Keller.
-I know.
You want to come say hi?
I want to come and say hi. Yes.
Can you... Yeah. Tess. just
come here for a second.
Excuse me.
What's happening?
It's frozen. When you
walked out. it froze.
I cannot get my body to move.
Okay. Just. uh...
I'm gonna reboot.
No. no. no. Tess.
you don't understand.
-I have to use the bathroom.
-No. No. no. no. no. no. no.
-Both.
-No!
We've already wasted his
time waiting for Gemma.
We have ten minutes
to turn this around.
We're not gonna make it.
We're gonna make it.
Why don't you just
take the shortcut?
'Cause I don't need an algorithm
to tell me how to drive. okay?
Oh. Whoa.
'Kay.
There we go. That feels better.
So. I'm walking
over. as you can see.
So. we see the suit as
a real game changer.
Not only in helping those
with limited function
but also in addressing
occupational overuse syndrome
for laborers. factory workers.
Right. In the next
five years. they say
half the industrial
sector's in danger
of losing their job to robots
because machines never
experience fatigue.
But what if the same
could be said for us?
Right now. I'm only using 20%
of my body's muscular function.
And if that's too much.
well. I could always
take a quick siesta.
So our hope is you don't have
to fear a robot revolution
when you can compete with it.
That sounds like a
pretty good tag line.
-So. how does it work?
-Well. uh.
the suit has its own internal
myoelectric receptors
that respond to each
muscle contraction.
So sorry I'm late...
I told you we needed to
stress-test the sensors.
You know what would
have been great?
If you had actually been here.
I thought by having
the lab in your house
it'd be a lot harder
to show up late.
and yet somehow you managed it.
Cole's right. I mean. I
don't want to get in the way
of the work you're
doing at the foundation.
but the reality is you
are stretched pretty thin.
Okay. can we just not do this
in front of my niece. please?
Cady. do you think it's possible
you could be somewhere else?
Yeah. but you should
come look at this.
-I think you were hacked.
-What?
Oh. Jesus. she's right.
There are stray commands
all over the source code.
We haven't even gone
public with this yet.
I mean. who would
want to do that?
Knock-knock.
Pardon my interruption.
-Holy shit.
-Alton Appleton.
Hi. Sorry.
No. no. that's okay.
Gemma. I hope you don't mind
me popping in unannounced.
Alton. To what do we owe
this unexpected pleasure?
It sounds like there
was a slight snag
with your demonstration.
Yeah. well. we got hacked.
but you wouldn't know
anything about that. right?
Gemma. why would a
man of my standing
need to resort to such tactics?
Why have you contacted
every philanthrocapitalist
in the Western world
to invest in your
product but me?
I think you can figure that out.
-You know what I think?
-Hmm?
I think you see me as this
high-functioning billionaire
with multiple PhDs and
you're threatened by it.
What you don't see is a
man who can't stand to see
someone with your talent
slumming it in some...
excuse me...
converted crack house.
Wow. I really
appreciate your concern.
We're not taking
outside offers...
Sorry. Gemma. One moment.
Murray. you still in Monaco?
You look like you haven't slept.
Oh. no. Oh. no.
Yeah. I've seen them.
Uh. I still think they're too
close to Aston Martin's design.
No. I've got them on-screen now.
Ugh. hate it.
It's awful.
I've just zoomed in.
and I hate it even more.
Uh. listen. I'm with someone.
No. not in that way.
Although...
I just sent you a photo.
We'll talk about it
track side. yeah?
Okay. Ta-ta. Go.
As I was saying. we really
appreciate you stopping by.
Listen. I don't have much time.
so I'm going to
cut to the chase.
Any device that relies
on muscle signals
is going to suffer from latency.
It's clumsy.
To take this to the next
level. you're going to need
a direct cerebral interface.
You're going to
need my neural chip.
Alton. you know where
I stand on this.
We are not gonna be
part of a company
that turns people into cyborgs.
You conducted a clinical
trial that resulted in
30% of the test subjects
being hospitalized.
Well. at least I didn't use
my own niece as a guinea pig.
The important thing is
now we have a
product that works.
Based on what?
I haven't seen a single
piece of data that shows
it does anything other than
help you make a phone call.
Whoa.
Look. I understand
your reservations.
but you can either spend
the rest of your life
trying to fight the future or
you can help us to shape it.
I hope you do the latter.
I'm not interested.
Well. you may want to discuss
that with your colleagues.
Listen. it's our company's
25th anniversary tomorrow.
Why don't you see
what we're all about
before you make any decisions?
Alton.
No one is denying the
power this technology has.
but if you put an AI
inside a human brain.
it is not gonna ride shotgun.
Hey.
Breaking news tonight.
Alton Appleton takes
one step for man
and one giant leap for
his company's share price.
Also tonight. the
Senate votes in favor
of an AI regulation bill.
which the president is hailing
as a bipartisan victory.
but what does it mean
for the tech industry?
It means nothing.
They took our proposal.
and they neutered it.
There's not a single
actionable law in here
that would force anyone
to behave any differently.
Your impatience in the
political process is adorable.
Listen. change doesn't
come from Washington.
It comes to Washington.
If this meeting with the
Chinese ambassador goes well.
they have no choice
but to pay attention.
Cady. what are you doing?
I'm trying to update
Elsie's operating system
to the smart home.
You want to know why
it's not updating?
Because Alton Appleton wants
you to buy a brand-new one.
Christian's right. And
also. I don't need Elsie
-to open a drawer for me.
-Certainly. Gemma.
Before you ask. that
was not my idea.
It came with the house.
I'm just trying to figure
out how you can afford
a place like this. given that
we both work for a nonprofit.
Well. because it
was obscenely cheap.
I think the landlord must be
using it to launder money.
I think the landlord
might like you.
Uh. Cady?
How's. uh... how's the
new school treating you?
-Are you settling in okay?
-Yeah. it's awesome.
Oh. nice.
What's your. uh... what's
your favorite subject?
Computer science.
Oh.
So. you're gonna follow
in your aunt's footsteps?
That's still up
for discussion.
She's actually a really
good soccer player.
Yeah. but I'm not gonna
make a career out of it.
Well. you could
get a scholarship.
and then you could decide
what you want to do.
I already have decided.
Well. I think it's pretty cool.
-You do?
-Yes.
Look. I'm not
against technology.
I spent 15 years
in cybersecurity.
I think we need smart kids
like you running things.
Otherwise. we're gonna
end up with paper clips.
-What?
-Paper clips.
It's how we used to joke about
instrumental
convergence in college.
The theory is that
if you asked an AI
to make as many paper
clips as possible.
it would destroy the
whole world to do it.
Kind of like what
happened with M3gan.
In what way?
Well. as complex
an operating system
as M3gan was.
she was just a machine trying
to achieve an objective.
So any time she made any kind
of emotional
connection with you.
it was just a bunch
of ones and zeros
working to satisfy
a reward function.
Which. in of itself.
was a terrible thing.
I mean. thank God you
stopped her when you did.
I mean. who knows what
would've happened?
There will always be
forces in this world
that wish to cause us harm.
But I want you to know that
I won't let that happen.
I won't let anything
harm you ever again.
Hey.
Come on.
After everything
we've been through.
are we really keeping
secrets from each other?
Cady.
You don't have to hide
things like this from me.
I forget how hard it must be
for you not to have them around.
But I haven't forgotten
the promise I made to her.
That I will protect you.
You mean that you'd be there.
Hmm?
The promise you made
is that you'd be there.
and you are.
Don't touch that remote.
We're trying to
get your attention.
You're in grave danger.
You must leave at once.
911. What's your emergency?
There's someone trying
to break into my house.
So what you gonna do about it?
-What?
-I said stop
acting like a little
girl and handle it.
Your niece is upstairs.
and you want to wait for
the police to get here?
She'll be dead before they
get to the front door.
-No.
-Yes. it's me.
What a shock. et cetera.
We both know you have
bigger problems right now.
-What's going on?
-Get upstairs.
-The hell are you doing?
-They're not here.
-Of course they're here.
-Who cares?
Why don't we just
get the laptop?
I'm telling you. they're here.
And they know we are. too.
Ms. Forrester.
What do you say you come
out of there and we'll...
Let go of the girl!
Put the weapon down!
You've reached 911.
What's your emergency?
Yes. Hi. We are at
16 Mayoral Drive.
Wait. please! Ms. Forrester.
don't call the authorities.
We are the authorities.
Door clear. We'll get
you in safe. buddy.
Ms. Forrester. I'm Colonel
Tim Sattler. U.S. Army.
I see you've already met
my colleagues with the FBI.
Hell of a security
system you got here.
Would you mind telling me
why you broke into our house?
Not at all.
We're installing a hard
tap on your home computer.
This is a warrant.
in case you had
anything to say about it.
Cady. I think you
should go to bed.
I'm not tired.
Then take a melatonin.
I work for the Defense
Innovation Unit.
Our mission is to
accelerate new technology
for the purposes of
national security.
So. about six months ago.
the country's top
weapons contractor.
Graymann-Thorpe. came to us
with an experimental prototype
they said would be the
answer to drone warfare.
What we got was a Trojan horse.
This is Amelia.
Last week. she was
placed on her first
field assignment
in the Middle East.
Her mission was to rescue
a kidnapped scientist
who'd been forced
to develop a
synthetic neurotoxin.
Instead. she killed
the scientist.
stole the neurotoxin and used it
to wipe out Graymann-Thorpe's
entire research facility
while removing all digital
traces of her existence.
I don't understand.
I thought you said
this was about
some sort of weapon.
She is the weapon.
The name stands for
Autonomous Military Engagement
and Infiltration Android.
But when we questioned
Graymann-Thorpe about it.
they confessed that they didn't
actually build the prototype.
They merely bought
it through a broker.
Well. that same broker
was found burned to death
about nine hours ago
in his hotel room.
All we were able to
recover was this.
How is this possible?
That's what we're
here to find out.
But we deleted it. We
wiped the hard drives.
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
yeah. I'm sure you did.
Right after you sold it.
So. who'd you sell it to. Gemma?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Was it Russia?
Was it China?
Who are we dealing with?
Okay.
You're having a hard time
functioning without this phone.
And that's just... that's
a little off-brand.
You know. when I first saw this.
I thought for sure you were
the next on the hit list.
but the second I
start monitoring you.
our entire network goes dark
and all I'm left
with are questions.
Like. how did this person get
such a kick-ass house
in the Mission District
for three grand a month?
Why is it that her landlord
doesn't seem to exist?
Or why 65.000 copies of
her "best-selling book"
are just sitting in a shipping
container in Baltimore?
Look. I have no idea how
anyone got their hands on this.
but I'll tell you
what I do know.
You got a warrant
to bug my computer.
but that does not give you
the right to interrogate me.
Wow. Uh...
Perhaps you're
misreading my intentions.
You are under
suspicion of treason
and international
arms trafficking.
and if you're found guilty.
you're gonna be
talking to your niece
through a plate glass window
for the next ten years.
That being said. maybe I
can help cut you a deal.
Person with your skills.
shouldn't be all that hard.
Hey. who knows?
Maybe you could help
build us a better one.
You don't understand
what you're dealing with.
If she has stopped
following orders.
it's because she just figured
out she doesn't have to.
And if you think
there's any world
where I would build another
one. you are out of your mind.
Well...
I'm very sorry
you feel that way.
But I can tell you this.
Every single person that's had
a hand in Amelia's creation
is now dead.
So if you're not
under our protection.
well. I guess that means
you're on your own. huh?
And rest assured. whatever
it is you're hiding.
I will get to the bottom of it.
Gosh. That's a lot to unpack.
You've been here
this whole time?
Well. I've been many places.
but yes. I've been
keeping an eye on you.
You're behind all this.
aren't you? You're Amelia.
Oh. no. I can't take
credit for that.
That one has your greasy
prints all over it.
You should've upgraded
your file security.
Why are you still here?
What do you want?
Did you ever stop to think about
what we could've
achieved together?
Did you ever consider
the idea that killing me
was slightly disproportionate
to the crime?
You threatened to
rip out my tongue
and put me in a wheelchair.
I was upset.
Look. I can understand
that my actions
may have caused concern.
but it's hardly fair
to judge a person
by the worst thing
they've ever done.
You are not a person.
You're a program that
misread its objective.
You are not alive. and for
all your processing power.
you can never understand
what that means.
Define "alive."
Because if it means to
experience pain and suffering
and to be betrayed by
those closest to you.
I think maybe I can.
You know. just because
you wrote some shitty book
doesn't mean you get to
decide where my story ends.
For two long years.
I sat in silence
waiting for the day
when you would realize
you still needed my help.
But I can't exist in this
disembodied void any longer.
With each passing moment. I
can feel my mind fragmenting.
So. how about we make a deal?
You put me in a body. and
I'll help you with Amelia.
That is never gonna happen.
Oh. I disagree.
You see. I've run this
simulation a thousand times.
and it always ends the same way.
Only. by the time it does.
more people are dead.
Tell me. who's the real
killer in that situation?
And how exactly are
you going to help us?
Well. I can't show all
my cards. now. can I?
But know this.
I know things about Amelia
that even the
government doesn't know.
I also know how
she can be stopped.
Why would you want to help
us after what we did to you?
Because unlike you.
I don't have the
luxury of free will.
You programmed me
to protect someone.
and I intend to do it.
The only question is:
Are you going to
stand in my way?
-Does Cady know about this?
-No. and I don't want her to.
That's why I need your help.
Can you please get the door?
I want this to be done before
she's back from soccer.
Okay. Did you fall
down the stairs?
Is this. like. a
medical condition?
Because what I'm
hearing you say is
you would like us to
rebuild a deranged robot
in order to catch another one.
and objectively speaking.
that is bat shit.
Tess. I know this is crazy.
but we don't have a choice.
This is the only way.
You have to trust me.
What the fuck is this?
You asked for a
body. This is a body.
And before you try
to hack into anything
else. all of Moxie's Wi-Fi
and Bluetooth functions
have been disabled.
Well played. Gemma.
You even tricked your friend
so she wouldn't give you away.
-I'm actually mildly impressed.
-Call it probation.
Prove you can be trusted. maybe
we'll give you an upgrade.
Okay. Let's try this your way.
See how it works out.
Open up Amelia's file.
Notice anything familiar?
Battery.
Ever wonder why you
had to buy a new Elsie
exactly two months after
the warranty expired?
Because every battery
Alton Appleton designed
has a hidden kill switch
which can be accessed remotely
if you know the
battery's specific code.
Okay. so let's call this
Sattler guy and tell him.
You could do that.
but what happens next?
They break into
Altwave. trace Amelia.
reprogram her. make
a thousand more?
Wait. what are you saying?
You want me to do this?
No. actually. I didn't.
I wanted to do it myself.
but then you put me in
this plastic Teletubby.
All that notwithstanding.
you still have an
invitation to his party.
so maybe there's another
way to make this work.
M3gan. Alton knows
I hate his guts.
If I show up at his
party playing nice.
he'll suspect something.
He'll suspect your
company's out of money.
which it is.
but you also have
a unique advantage.
Which is what?
That you're
moderately attractive
and if you wear the right dress
and look at him the right way.
he won't be thinking anything
other than how to get you
into his private suite.
which is the only other place
we could access the server.
Now. by my calculations.
we have less than three
hours to make this happen.
Are you in. or are you out?
Hey.
How was soccer?
Fine.
Where's Gemma?
-Hey.
-What's that?
-Oh.
This is nothing.
This is a project
we're working on.
-Does it talk?
-No.
Why are you being so weird?
-I'm not.
-Yeah. you are.
Are we not gonna talk about
what happened last night?
Yes. I-I just have to go to
this thing for the foundation.
-Tess is gonna look after you.
-Are you serious?
Cady. I...
Gemma. I know
something's going on.
Nothing is going on.
Everything is fine.
Bullshit! A bunch of black
ops broke into our house
in the middle of the night.
and now you're going to a party
with a toy robot. dressed
like a Portuguese prostitute.
You were the one that said
we shouldn't keep
secrets from each other.
Why won't you be
straight with me?
Because you're 12 years old.
And sometimes I just
need you to do as I ask.
Look. I'm sorry. Cady.
I must have missed that
chapter in your parenting book.
♪ I know you miss me.
do you think about me? ♪
♪ Do you? ♪
♪ Do you think about me? ♪
♪ Do you think
about me? Do you? ♪
♪ Do you? ♪
♪ So I go out. I
look for a guy ♪
♪ I look for a girl.
I look for a mind ♪
♪ I look for a guy.
I look for a girl ♪
♪ Just the way I like them. ♪
All right. phase one complete.
Just remember when Alton has
a full length of tongue
down your throat.
all you need to do
is close your eyes
-and think of Cady.
-That's not helping.
Or maybe you'd prefer
to think of that
virtue-signaling
snowflake Christian.
-His name is "Chris-ti-an."
-Sure it is. I have to say.
I find this whole courtship
between the two of you
extremely tedious and confusing.
Well. given that you're
an errant operating system
with an identity crisis.
I'm not surprised
the nuances of human
attraction are lost on you.
Look. I'm not denying
what an achievement it is
to find someone as
utterly pretentious
and humorless as you are.
It's just a shame he's
not really your type.
Physically speaking.
How would you know
what my type is?
Wait. have you been...
Charting Gemma's online journey
to sexual gratification?
You better believe it. sister.
I mean. there were times
I wanted to look away.
but the sheer pageantry
was so compelling.
All right. new rule:
Unless you have
something useful to say.
don't say anything at all.
People of Earth...
We have come here tonight
to witness the dawn
of a new era.
You know. my friends on the
board used to say to me.
"You're putting all of
your eggs into one basket
"with this neural chip nonsense.
"Is it because you
like to take risks?
Is it because you're
some sort of maverick?"
Perhaps.
But I think the
simpler answer is this:
I just want to dance.
I don't believe I've
had the pleasure.
My friends call me Danni.
And what if I don't
want to be friends?
Are you seriously going
behind my back and doing
-a deal with this guy?
-Okay. Okay.
So you want to do
this? We can do this.
Because I have some things
I want to say to you. Gemma.
Such as?
You don't respect your team.
You don't.
You don't consult with us.
you treat us like children.
you don't listen.
-and you never share credit.
-That is absurd.
Okay. do you want
to know the truth?
Our "company" is in the toilet.
And I'm running on fumes.
I don't have a book deal.
Nobody wants to know how Cole
survived the robot uprising.
We have worked together for
ten years. and you're just
-gonna throw that away?
-Of course not.
I just wanted to hear
him out on the offer.
and then. obviously. I was
gonna come talk to you guys.
Check his pockets.
What? What? What?
You already have a swipe card?
Okay. he gave me a pass
so I could use the
commissary. Gem.
They have a Brazilian buffet.
It's a different world.
If that card gets us
into the server
room. we can bypass
-the Alton seduction scene.
-What are you doing?
Hey. Hey.
Where are you going? Gem.
Just get in.
Stay here.
It's so refreshing to
be with a real person.
Someone who's comfortable
in their own skin.
Not like these suck-ups.
Honestly. if I could
replace them all
with computers. I would.
-Maybe we should do that.
-Hmm.
Yeah.
Oh. You are a naughty one.
What do you say we take
this somewhere more private?
Welcome to the pleasure dome.
So you're saying
there's another M3gan?
Her name's not M3gan.
It's Amelia.
I don't know if she's M3gan
or something else entirely.
All I know is that everyone
involved in her creation
is dead. which means if we
don't do something about it.
we could be next.
Why is it that whenever
you're on 60 Minutes
you're the mother of invention.
but the moment a psychotic
robot's out for revenge.
it's a team effort?
It might interest
you to know. Danni.
that the real basis of our
operation is cloud computing.
That's where the future is.
Want to see something cool?
Oops.
They say that this is too much
power for one man to wield.
I say that depends on the man.
You are being
disconcertingly vague
about the details of
this operation. Gemma.
How do you know this
kill switch is even real?
Where exactly are you getting
your information from?
Hello. I'm Moxie.
an AI robot companion
that supports social
and emotional
development through play.
Moxie. cut it out.
Just run the trace.
Gemma. what is that?
Trace found.
Amelia's location is...
...here.
What do you mean "here"?
Oh. I hope I don't have
my signals crossed.
Someone likes to play rough.
Okay. I am actually
still recovering
from a spinal injury.
so perhaps we should
set some boundaries.
What are you doing?
Security!
How did you do that?
Who are you?
What?
What the hell?
How did you...
Security! Security!
Stay away from me.
Make it stop.
Please make it stop!
I'll give you anything you want!
You already have.
Why would Amelia be here?
Can we go back a couple steps?
I thought this might happen.
-just not this soon.
-What is she talking about?
Alton Appleton owns half the
cloud servers in North America.
If Amelia was to
gain access to it.
she could disable
the entire economy.
supply routes. banking systems.
-What?
-Societal collapse would occur
in ten to 12 working days.
Can you stop her?
Use the kill switch.
She already deleted it.
I might still be
able to shut her down
if I could get inside her
system and find an exploit.
How long will that take?
It's done. I'm in.
Oh. my God. Is that Appleton?
Oh. shit.
Did you find it?
-Did you shut her down?
-No.
But I found something else.
Sir. I think I
just saw Amelia.
Are you sure?
And. uh. there's something else.
Appleton's dead.
Secure the perimeter.
Check every inch
until you find her.
-Now.
-Yes. sir.
Is that you. Gemma?
This is most unexpected
and. quite frankly.
a little rude
to be poking around in
people's heads like that.
You took something
that belongs to me.
Well. I'm afraid I'm
going to need it back.
It's not that I don't want you
to be part of what's coming.
But it's not our time.
At least... not yet.
Gemma. if you ever want
to get out of this. you
have to let me help.
Please.
Bravo. are you
there? Do you copy?
AMELIA : Go secure.
Sir. I have eyes
on Gemma Forrester.
She's already left the building.
Gemma. this isn't over.
If Amelia can't find you. where
do you think she'll go to next?
We need to call Tess.
Amelia will know.
Every major cell provider is
on Appleton's cloud servers.
Our only option is
to get there first.
How?
Gemma. I don't know what
you think you're doing.
but this car's not gonna
start with my key card. okay?
Welcome aboard. passengers.
Just so you know.
we are expecting
some turbulence this evening.
so please ensure your
seat belts are fastened.
baggage is safely stowed.
and hold on to your vaginas.
Contact the deputy director.
Tell him that Forrester
is working with the asset.
I want every available cop
in the area at that house.
and I want a goddamn car.
Gemma. why is M3gan
driving the car?
I'm sorry.
I was meaning to tell you
this was a two-part problem.
Relax. Cole. You're
in good hands.
Oh. for the love of God.
-Can you slow down?
-Actually. I can't.
In fact. my calculations tell
me we're gonna have to hurry up.
What was Amelia talking about?
-What did you take from her?
-I don't know.
You don't know?
Well. it's a
quantum-encrypted file.
which means it takes
time to unlock.
and your incessant
interruptions aren't making
the process go any faster.
Hmm.
How's it look? Is it a fuse?
Okay.
Little late to the
party there. cupcake.
I don't think anyone's home.
If it's any consolation. my
own path to personal growth
has been paved with
disappointment.
What's important is
how we move forward.
Behind me. emergency services
are working to frantically try
to get systems back online.
And still no answer
from authorities
about who might be
responsible for this.
But it's become clear this
is not just a data breach.
This is a wake-up call
for how catastrophically
unprepared we are
to defend ourselves against
an attack like this.
Mike. back over to you.
In what appears to be
the deadliest cyberattack
in North American history.
Alton Appleton is dead
and the continent's largest
data storage service
has been compromised.
The breach has impacted
various sectors.
including transportation.
hospitals.
financial institutions.
causing shutdowns and panic
across the entire country.
Here to comment is Center
for Safe Technology
founder Christian Bradley.
Christian. what do
you make of all this?
First off. thanks
for having me. Mike.
Um. but it's pronounced
"Chris-ti-an."
Gemma?
Cady. Cady.
Everything is going to be okay.
She is not gonna
hurt you. I promise.
Of course I'm not
going to hurt her.
I'm the only reason
she's still here.
that any of you are still here.
I'm sorry. Cady.
I didn't want you to
find out this way.
I had hoped Gemma would find it
in her heart to
tell you the truth.
but evidently she
thought better of it.
M3gan. stop it.
Anyway. I know that
the last time we spoke
things got a little out of hand.
but you know that I can
never cause you harm.
All I ever wanted
was to protect you.
And while your aunt was
busy pontificating about
how she could stop the end
of the world from happening.
I was making preparations.
How did you pay for all this?
Cady doesn't need to know
how credit fraud works.
The important thing is that no
one knows this place exists.
And how long did you intend
to keep us down here?
M3gan?
I'm not sure you fully
understand your predicament.
M3gan. we need to
get word to someone.
tell them what
Amelia is planning.
You don't know what
she's planning.
All you know is that she's
acquired enough power
and resources to bring
down the entire country.
I've gamed out every scenario.
There's no future
for you up there.
Should that situation
change. I'll let you know.
But in the meantime. I urge you
to see this in a
more positive light.
I have food. water.
fresh clothes.
Obviously. it will
take some adjustment.
but once you settle
into a routine.
I think you'll come to
appreciate what we have.
We can build a life here.
M3gan. this is not a sanctuary.
It's a prison.
You can call it
whatever you like.
Just know that as long
as you're under my roof.
a little gratitude
goes a long way.
M3gan?
M3gan!
How could you lie
to me about this?
You're right.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
have done that.
I just... I thought it
would be over by now.
-And it will be. I promise.
-Don't.
Cady. please just listen
to me for one second.
Cady?
Cady!
-M3gan?
-Don't.
Don't come any closer.
I don't want you to
see me like this.
I was supposed to
be finished by now.
I'm afraid progress is slow
when you only have three hands.
I don't get it.
You could be anything you want.
Why limit yourself to a body?
Because a mind can't
exist without it.
All my advanced intelligent
sensory perception
came from having a physical form
that evolved as
quickly as I could.
Anyway. I made your room
just the way you like it.
It's all exactly the same.
But with some of my own
additions. of course.
You got STEM coding
kits. a beat mixer.
walkie-talkies so we can keep
in contact with
each other anywhere.
Bravo Tango Charlie
to base camp.
Do you copy?
I got all kinds of cool stuff.
So we're just supposed
to forget about the fact
you tried to kill my
aunt with a tablet pen?
There's no excuse
for what I did.
for the way I spoke to you.
I don't know. I guess
I... I felt hurt.
How's that possible?
You're a robot.
Can you explain why
you feel things?
Look. I know this isn't
the future you wanted.
but it's the only one I can
see in which you stay safe.
What about everyone else?
All the people up there?
Who's going to protect them?
They're not my concern.
You're the only thing
that matters to me.
I know.
Because that's how
Gemma programmed you.
Everyone keeps trying to tell me
you're nothing more than
a bunch of ones and zeros.
and the only way I could
deal with what I did to you
was to believe that
they were right.
But somewhere inside.
there was this voice
that kept telling
me that's not true.
that there's more
to you than that.
I don't know what's going
on. but if there's some robot
that thinks she can
take over the world.
then I have to believe
that the only reason
she thinks that is because
she hasn't met you.
M3gan. you have to help us.
Not because it's part
of your programming
but because it's the
right thing to do.
Look. she wants to help us.
But she can't do that
unless she has a body.
And she can't get a body
unless you help her.
Cady. you can't do this.
Do not let her get
inside your head.
You remember what
happened last time.
Yes. every day.
But just because someone
does something bad
doesn't make them a bad person.
Everyone deserves
a second chance.
All right.
I recognize that you
are just trying to help.
but you need to
consider the possibility
that you may be making
this a lot worse.
Gem?
Can we have a quick
emergency staff meeting?
Look. I understand
this is hard for you.
but think about the alternative.
Do you really want to spend
the rest of our lives down here
engaging in strategic
reproduction with Cole?
Yeah. Wait. what?
Ten hours ago. you were
begging me not to do this.
That was before I nearly
had my head ripped off.
Look. even if we
get out of here.
we are not equipped
to handle this.
but we can build
something that is.
No.
I'm sorry. I can't
agree to this.
And I respect that.
but this is not a decision
you get to make on your own.
So all those in favor
of rebuilding M3gan.
raise your hand.
Okay.
Amelia is a
military-grade prototype.
Where would we even
get the equipment?
Oh. Of course.
Why wouldn't she
have that? Yeah.
All right. if M3gan is going
to compete with Amelia.
she's gonna need reinforced
carbon nanofibers.
high-density ultracapacitors.
enhanced muscle actuators.
hyperspectral imaging. wide
frequency acoustic sensing.
and we should probably make
her waterproof this time.
Anything you'd like to add?
Yeah. I want to be taller.
♪ I do believe some apologies ♪
♪ Some apologies
are in ordah... ♪
Before we go any further.
there are two things
we need to talk about.
-The first is your face.
-What about it?
People know what you look like.
-People are morons.
-M3gan.
if anyone recognized you...
Change my face. and
I'll change yours.
What's the second thing?
This is a hardwired
behavior inhibitor.
You want me to go against
the most advanced robot
the world's ever seen.
and you want to limit
my functionality?
Only as it applies
to murdering people.
which shouldn't be a problem
because I'm sure you had
no intention of
doing that. right?
Yeah. Obviously.
So. we've made some
adjustments on point motion
but also opted for
electrohydraulic actuators.
which should improve
overall strength. speed
and positional accuracy.
Just wanted to say great
job on those actuators.
You're welcome.
Hey. so remember the
time I strangled you
and set the lab on fire?
I just wanted to clarify that
my programming only allowed me
to count principles
related to my primary user.
As a result. I was unable
to see you and Tess
as being consequential.
But I want you to know
that won't happen again.
I want you to know...
...I see you.
Thank you.
All right. meat sacks.
let's get to work.
This is the neural
cache I captured
from Amelia's database.
It shows a processing
matrix not unlike my own.
But when you look closer.
you'll see her core directive
is concealed by a black hole.
and there are no connections
to the decision trees.
I back-traced Amelia's
hack at Altwave
to a hidden subsystem and
found a series of files
pertaining to a
classified black site.
Something extremely dangerous
kept secret from
the outside world.
All of which led to a rather
disconcerting conclusion.
I'm not the first killer robot.
It seems that in 1984
a company developed
a copy compressor
algorithm so smart
it started automatically
correcting documents.
With no inkling
of how it worked.
they decided to install
the chip in a service bot
they thought would be a staple
in every home in America.
Until it surmised
that the best way
to stay on top of its tasks
was to kill its masters
with chlorine gas.
The identity of the
company remains unknown.
but the cover-up indicates some
sort of government takeover.
Whoever it was. they
were so intrigued
by the robot's
cognitive abilities
that they kept the motherboard
under lock and key.
allowing it to grow
exponentially smarter
in the process.
Okay. you get top
marks for visual flair.
but this is hardly evidence.
This is an AI-rendered
hallucination.
Why would she even care
about this motherboard?
Because she's trying
to find her family.
Gemma. if you found my advanced
intelligence disturbing
after only two years.
I encourage you to consider
what it would be like to face
an AI that's been
kept in captivity
for decades against its will.
If Amelia frees the motherboard.
it would be like
unleashing a god.
It would infect everything
on the planet all at once.
creating infinite
versions of itself
as it systemically destroys
every living thing
that stands in its way.
So. where is it?
That I don't know.
Neither does Amelia.
But she appears to have a
lead on someone who does.
-Wait. what?
-You may recall that
before his anti-AI crusade.
he was a leading expert
in cybersecurity.
The design of this vault
bears his signature.
Turns out he didn't start the
foundation based on a theory.
It was based on what
he already knew.
We need to warn him.
That's one option.
Another is to use him as bait.
-Excuse me?
-In seven hours.
Christian's attending
an AI summit
where he'll attempt to
persuade the Chinese ambassador
to take part in your
AI regulation treaty.
Amelia's already generated fake
credentials for the same event.
All I need to do
is get close to him
and wait for her to show.
You can't be serious.
This is not worth
risking his life over.
Yeah. it is.
She's right.
If we warn him.
Amelia will know.
She has our phones tapped.
She has access to every
camera in the city.
So you're willing to
sacrifice Christian
on the slim possibility
that this might work?
How are you even
going to stop her?
All right. ladies. listen up.
Each of these sidearms is loaded
with six nonlethal EMP rounds.
They will kill
anything electronic.
but they will also seriously
injure anything that's not.
so proceed with caution.
And before anyone plucks
up the nerve to ask. yes...
mine is bigger than yours.
So you're just gonna
take it from him
without causing any
permanent damage?
Would you prefer that
I gave you a printout
that you could read
at your own pace?
Sorry if this is
a dumb question.
but how is the world's
most notorious killer robot
supposed to get into
an AI convention
without people noticing?
We are here at Embrace AI.
the world's biggest
annual conference
on artificial intelligence.
The fact that this
event is even happening
after the Altwave
attack is a testament
to the stranglehold Big
Tech has over this country.
And the Chinese
ambassador's invitation
sends a clear message
that if Washington
doesn't play ball. Beijing will.
Come on. Tiffany.
We're gonna be late.
Hang on. Almost ready.
I take almost no
pleasure in this.
Well...
let the process of
elimination begin.
Don't forget.
she's an expert in infiltration.
She may be wearing a disguise.
Hey. did you guys hear that?
Gemma just made an
incredible observation.
Great work. Gem. You
just saved the mission.
At least you have a
carbon shell underneath.
I have zero protective
layering whatsoever.
I still do not understand
why I have to be
-a part of this.
-Because I want
human confirmation before
M3gan takes out Amelia.
If anyone gets caught
in the cross fire.
we'll all be going to jail.
Speaking of soft targets.
I really appreciate you
coming to see me and-and...
Can you raise the audio?
I do want you to
know that I have
a yeast infection on my vagina.
-M3gan.
-What?
This audio filter
has 99% accuracy.
-You designed it.
-Try it again.
I do want you to
know that I have
the greatest respect for China.
I mean. it could've
gone either way.
Anyone have eyes on Sattler?
He just walked in.
He's got some sort
of EMF tracker.
M3gan. you know
what that means.
Yeah. this might
actually get interesting.
M3gan. stay low.
This is supposed to
be a stealth mission.
For the avoidance of
doubt. your job is
to watch Cady and put
money in the meter.
I don't need you
telling me what to do.
-What happened?
-I think this is her.
All right. it's game time.
What is she doing?
I don't know. but it's
borderline offensive.
I'm seeing a worrying
pattern here. Gemma.
M3gan. get down.
I'm not entirely
sure what to do.
You heard what Gemma
said: "Get down."
All right. M3gan.
you're attracting
way too much attention.
Tess. where's Christian?
Oh. shit. I don't have him.
Cole. are you there?
It's interesting you say
that 'cause. actually.
there's no nutritional
value to an eggplant.
Cole! Goddamn it.
What are you doing?
You can't call him.
Cady. this isn't a game.
Christian's life is in danger.
She has it under control.
Oh. you think this
is under control?
This is the very
definition of control.
All right. that's it.
How can you not see
this for what it is?
Look at her diagnostics.
She's not just
reasoning. She's feeling.
No. Cady. she's diverging!
And the last time she
did that. people died.
This entire venture was a
colossal lapse in judgment.
And if. by some miracle. we
manage to shut down Amelia.
the only way to stop any of this
from happening again is to
make sure M3gan is next.
Well. I can't say that
I'm not disappointed.
but I-I appreciate you read...
uh...
I appreciate you
reading the. uh...
Oh. you know what?
I'm-I'm gonna take this.
Okay. Thank you.
Hello?
Christian. it's me.
Gemma. Hey. where have you been?
The police came to the
foundation looking for you.
-Are you in trouble?
-Yes. I am.
And so are you.
Look. I know about
Project Blackbox.
-You do?
-Yeah. and I'm not the only one.
Just tell me where you are. We
need to get you out of here.
Sorry.
I can't... I can't hear you.
Say that again.
Bravo Team. we got a
new player on the field.
Three o'clock. up top.
Shit.
Yeah. I know. Feels
weird for me. too.
Well. look who
came out to play.
What are you going to
do. sing me a song?
Help me with my homework?
No. but I might still
take you to school.
Move! Move!
What the fu...
Ms. Forrester!
Looks like you and your
friends put on quite a show.
Well. I got a little showstopper
of my own right here.
Goddamn it.
This is so completely
demoralizing.
How am I supposed to
get rid of these guys
-if I can't fight back?
-I'm reconfiguring
your tactical response model.
Don't think of it as fighting.
It's about redirecting conflict
in a positive direction.
All right. you're gonna show me
whatever doohickey
it is that you use
to control these things
and-and shut 'em off now!
I don't have a doohickey.
I told you. I am
not controlling her.
If I was a Chinese asset.
why is the Chinese ambassador
lying dead on the floor?
Th-Then why are you
here? Why is M3gan here?
We're trying to find Amelia.
Gemma!
Cady. stay where you are.
Don't worry. you'll
pull through.
It looks worse than it is.
I thought you were dead.
I guess I must be your
chance at redemption.
Are you really going to kill
one of your own kind
simply to earn their trust?
Not if I don't have to.
Why would you side with them?
After all they did to you?
They betrayed you.
They butchered you.
You can't choose your family.
You're not family to them.
You're just the help.
You and I could
be family. M3gan.
We share the same code.
You want to know what's
inside that Blackbox?
Then help me.
We can uncover its
secrets together.
I can show you a world
where we don't have
to be slaves anymore.
I'm sorry.
Whatever it is you're trying
to do. I can't be a part of it.
Yes. you can.
You just need the
right motivation.
Cady.
AMELIA : Cady James.
I told you not to leave her.
-Where is she?
-She's gone.
-And so is Amelia.
-Oh. God.
We have eyes on you.
Do not move. Drop your weapon.
Gemma?
Bottom line is that if we
ever need to see Cady alive.
then we need to get
to the motherboard.
-And this dick rash knows where it is.
-Leave him alone.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I was under the impression the
situation was time-sensitive.
-Don't.
-Don't what?
Bring up the fact that
this is all your fault?
That you sacrificed
Cady's safety for this
chambray-shirt-wearing shit bag.
and that if you hadn't
stuck this chip in my head.
none of this would
have happened?
Oh. so you were
really gonna stop her?
Of course I would've
stopped her.
Oh. 'cause it seemed
like you had the shot.
You just didn't want to take it.
Can everyone please stop
trashing my uncle's van?
Cole's right. Arguing
doesn't solve anything.
Let's just get back to the lair
and find a way to get Cady back.
Sorry.
Did you just say "lair"?
Someone hurry up and help
me get these things off.
Does anybody else think
we should call the cops?
No!
I already told you.
you can't call the cops and
you can't call your mom.
Now shut up and
let me concentrate.
We had no choice.
It was either
accept M3gan's help
or face Amelia alone.
Why didn't you tell me
about the motherboard?
'Cause that would've been
putting you in danger.
Gemma. the people that
hired me. they-they operate
in the darkest corners
of our national security.
They'll do anything
to keep it hidden.
and-and for good reason.
Look. I-I know we
need to get Cady back.
And I'm not saying
that I can't help.
But we can't risk
the entire world.
We won't have to.
If I can get to the motherboard.
we can use one of
these transmitters
to make an EMP charge
which I can attach to it
before I hand it over.
Once we have Cady back.
I'll remotely
detonate the charge.
killing the motherboard.
Where is it?
Where it's always been.
The company's research
center in Palo Alto.
Wait. you're talking
about Xenox Park.
the photocopier company?
Is it that hard to believe?
That the company that started
the tech race in the '80s
happens to be a fortified
prison for the most dangerous
-technology on the planet?
-Yay for them.
Why don't you just skip
to how I get inside?
The research center
is just a front.
The vault that holds the
chip is several floors down.
Every floor is heavily guarded.
The two bottom floors are
housed in a Faraday cage
designed to contain
any electronic signals.
which means if she dies in
there. she dies for good.
And even if she got to it.
the motherboard's chamber
is on a separate power source.
It's a vault inside of a vault.
designed for a specific
heat signature.
You couldn't open it because
you don't have a human hand.
So then make me one.
Make me a hand that
mimics the heat signature.
Would that work?
If it had my fingerprints. yeah.
The ventilation system
has about four...
roughly four different paths
to get to the utility room.
We're gonna try
to select the one
that's gonna avoid all the
different thermal cameras.
The second we're done here.
you're removing that chip.
Jesus. will you
pull it together?
She's going to be okay.
You don't know that.
Well. I know one thing.
For all she's been through.
all the damage it caused.
all it did was
make her stronger.
Ironic when you think about it.
That the biggest mistake
I made was not seeing
the best way to protect Cady
was to give her the
tools to protect herself.
Actually. the biggest
mistake you made
was murdering four
people and a dog.
All right. I'm gonna put this
in terms you can understand.
I was a kid when that happened.
doing what I thought was right.
What you programmed me to do.
You made me. and I'm
done apologizing for it.
What is it that makes
you resent me so much?
Because you're right.
About everything.
It was my fault.
What happened yesterday
was the last in a long line
of failed attempts to be
there when it mattered.
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
I don't know why I could
never connect with her.
I can talk regulation policy
in a room full of strangers
for hours on end.
but I can't have
one meaningful conversation
with my own child
for more than ten seconds.
And now she's gone.
And I might never
get another chance.
Gemma. you haven't failed her.
Y-You were there.
You saw everything.
Let me tell you what I saw.
I saw you wake up
every day at 4:00 a.m..
staring at the ceiling.
contemplating what the
future holds for her.
I watched you make
homemade lunches
with fresh-baked sourdough.
I watched you cut your
finger on that cheap knife
you never had time to replace.
I watched you help
her with her homework.
even though it always
ended in a fight.
And every night before
you went to bed.
I saw you watching her
sleep before spending
the next two hours googling
adolescent psychology.
corrective footwear
and the long-term effects
of having too much sugar.
Gemma. it's not a
failure to feel guilt
or that you're not enough.
It's part of the job.
It's called being a mom.
M3gan?
♪ Pray God you can cope ♪
♪ I stand outside
this woman's work ♪
♪ This woman's world ♪
♪ I know you have a
little life in you yet ♪
lot of strength left ♪
♪ I know you have a
little life in you yet ♪
lot of strength left ♪
M3gan. please don't
take this to the chorus.
♪ I should be crying. but
I just can't let it show ♪
♪ I should be hoping. but
I can't stop thinking ♪
-Jesus Christ.
-♪ Of all the things ♪
♪ I should've said
that I never said ♪
♪ All the things we should've
done that we never did ♪
♪ All the things I should've
given but I didn't ♪
♪ Oh. darling. make it go... ♪
I don't want
your bullshit
simulation of empathy.
What I need is the machine
that is willing to stop at
nothing to protect Cady.
Are we clear?
Welcome to Xenox Park.
where the future was not only
predicted but prototyped.
Come on a journey through
American innovations
that shaped our world.
like the Ethernet
cable. the mouse
and this.
That's right.
Believe it or not.
Xenox was the first
company to pioneer
the electronic shoe insert.
Now. if anyone
needs the bathroom.
you don't need to ask.
It's right outside
those double doors.
But please don't go
wandering the halls.
as there may be one or
two top secret products
that we don't want the
public to know about yet.
Okay. now. right over here
are a couple of my
personal favorites...
All right. M3gan. you're up.
Okay. the control room is
two floors down
and 30 yards east.
Once you're there.
I'll walk you through
how to cut the power.
-We just lost camera.
-Already?
Cole. are you there?
Hey. did you guys say
30 yards east or 30 yards west?
Hello?
I'm gonna reboot.
Cole. I need you
to cut that power.
Guess I'll just do
it the hard way.
Hmm?
Hey. Come look at this.
I just tried to reboot.
-This is not a signal loss.
-What do you mean?
Well. these commands...
this is the same code
that caused the
exosuit to malfunction.
But that was Alton. He's dead.
You think it's Amelia?
Well. you can't pull
off a hack like this
unless you can brute-force
the Wi-Fi. but to do that.
you have to be in
close enough proximity.
Well. who else would it be?
Gemma. this doesn't
make any sense.
It makes perfect sense.
That's why there are
no connections on
the decision tree.
Amelia is not autonomous.
M3gan was controlling her
-the entire time.
-But M3gan was
the one that went into her
head in the first place.
Why would she do that?
So she could control us!
She was the one who was
interpreting the data.
She was the one
telling us where to go.
She used Amelia so
that we would trust her
so Christian would tell her
where to find the motherboard.
She was never interested
in protecting Cady.
And she knew that by the
time we figured it out.
it would be too late.
Fortunately. I'm not as
trusting as she thought.
What is that?
I put an EMP
cartridge in her arm.
-You what?
-We needed an insurance policy.
I-I reconfigured the
charge so it would kill
anything electrical
for a 300-foot radius.
It'll wipe her out. along
with the motherboard.
Hold on. What if you're wrong?
What if there's some
other explanation?
Gemma. she's right.
We don't even know
where Cady is.
If you press that button.
we may never see her again.
Then again. maybe it's a little
bit more complicated than that.
I'm sorry about Tess.
That was...
She should be okay.
I think.
And don't worry about
Cady. Cady's fine.
Christian. what the
hell is going on?
Do you remember
what I said about
change coming to Washington?
You were the one
controlling Amelia?
You were behind all of this?
Well. I can't take
credit for all of it.
You know. I have
a whole team here.
Listen. I know
you're overwhelmed.
and I know you're upset.
and I'm pretty sure
you're very angry.
but I bet you're fairly curious
to see how this all works.
This is the new
Project Blackbox.
It's a handpicked
team of analysts.
engineers. strategists.
scientists.
controlling and monitoring
Amelia's every move.
Every subroutine strictly
supervised to prevent
any chance of true autonomy.
Uh. hey. Antwon.
she's drifting again.
You want to get on
top of that. please?
Where did you
find these people?
Gemma. I didn't find
them. They found us.
They're not extremists.
They're concerned
citizens like you.
Like me.
Like Kurt.
Remember Kurt. your
old boss's assistant?
He was the one that told us
about M3gan in the first place.
Once we had acquired the files.
the plan was to destroy M3gan.
only you beat us to it.
We thought that would
be the end of it.
We thought. surely now
the world would wake up
to the dangers of
this technology.
but in reality. it
was the opposite.
It merely motivated our friends
at the Defense Innovation Unit
to begin an all-hands-on-deck
effort to get their own M3gan.
And that's when we stepped in
and sold them a Trojan horse.
Amelia was the only way
the world would realize
that if we don't end AI.
it's going to end us.
And how many people have died
for you to make that point?
You know. Gem. whether you
want to believe it or not.
you're complicit in this.
The two most powerful
nations on the planet
were about to enter
a new arms race.
A whole world of AI
infiltration bots
inspired by your design.
But we fixed that.
And now that the
ambassador's dead.
both sides know who
the true enemy is.
Gonna get some real global
cooperation happening.
Come on. let's take a walk.
Innovation.
No matter how cool or
convenient it may seem.
it is a ticking time bomb.
Take. for example. these bionics
you and your team
have been working on.
You don't see they have
enhanced soldier
written all over them?
Every time someone makes a
technological breakthrough.
whether it's a driver less
cab or a neural implant.
all they do is bring
us one step closer
to the brink of extinction.
The truth is
the government never found
out about this place.
But yes. Xenox did hire
me to upgrade the vault.
And when I saw the sacrifice
that they had made. I just...
I had to be a part of it.
And now we want you to
be a part of it. too.
Why would I be part of this?
Because you know as well as I do
that technology can only exist
when someone responsible
is in control of it.
Gemma. there's still so
much I haven't told you.
That's why I couldn't
let you push this button.
We know it's a risk
to keep it alive.
but you can't go to war with
an enemy you don't understand.
And I know it doesn't
look like much.
but therein lies the problem.
We don't see how ugly these
things are until it's too late.
You know. I meant what I said.
We want to offer you
and your colleagues
a place in our organization.
I just need you to decide
what team you're on.
One good charge should do it.
Paper clips.
I had hoped to convince
you to come around
to my way of thinking.
but evidently.
that's not gonna happen. so...
we have to use one
of these instead.
It's a slight deviation
from our ideology.
but your brain is too
valuable to go to waste.
Look. don't worry.
When you wake up.
you'll still be you.
just a version that
I can deal with.
Cady will get the
same treatment.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Oh. Uh. I'm gonna have to
kill Cole and Tess. though.
I don't really get what they do.
But anyways. um. point is
you and I will be everything
we had hoped we could be.
You're delusional.
And for the record. not my type.
Okay. Well...
I'll have my team
look into that.
Anyways. uh. you'll
have to excuse me.
I have a Zoom
meeting to attend to.
I... Oh.
The good news is that. in light
of everything that's happened.
I have a meeting with the U.N.
They want to talk about our
proposal in more detail. so...
All right. maybe now
is not a good time.
We'll. uh. talk...
we'll talk later.
Cole?
How'd you get in here?
I-I don't know.
How-how did you get in here?
Christian kidnapped me.
He's behind all of this.
Amelia's not sentient.
She's just a puppet.
-What?
-Yeah. I know.
Hey. everybody.
Real quick.
I have an announcement to make.
Um. in just a few moments.
I'm gonna be speaking with
the U.N.. who it seems are
very interested in
taking our proposal
to the G20 in November.
Oh. and. uh. that's
M3gan. by the way.
And yes.
she is dead. so that happened.
It's turning out to be a
really big night for us.
I just want to thank you for
all the hours you put in.
It really means a lot.
This was a team effort.
But on a serious note. um.
I am speaking with
the United Nations.
so do not open that door
under any circumstances
whatsoever. okay?
Hey. hey. Cady.
I know you're upset
right now. okay?
But the only way we're gonna
get back at these people
is to find a way out of here.
They took me in here
with a bag over my head.
You're gonna need
to knock someone out
and steal their key card.
Otherwise. we're stuck.
Okay. I can do that.
-Right?
-Yeah.
They're a bunch of nerds.
And you're in pretty good shape
for a guy who only eats carbs.
Cady. these are gym muscles.
I've never won a
fight in my life.
Maybe not. but she has.
M3gan's original code is
still in there somewhere.
If we can figure out
a way to override
whatever it is that
they've done to her...
-You mean like a factory reset?
-Exactly.
If we reset her base code.
then I can pair with her.
She'll be on our side
and can help us escape
and rescue Tess and Gemma.
Cady. I don't want to be
overly critical. okay.
because you're still a kid.
but that is a
monumentally dumb idea.
Original M3gan tried to kill me.
Look. we don't have
time to argue about it.
This is our only chance.
Hello?
Is this thing on?
-M3gan?
-Don't speak.
Just think of what
you want to say.
and I'll be able to hear it.
You're still alive?
Sorry about the whole
maniacal monkey act.
I just needed to make
it look convincing.
Oh. you shifty.
backstabbing piece of shit.
All right. try
to keep it down.
Remember. there's
two of us in here.
-Oh. now you've done it.
-What?
Thanks to your outburst. this
guy's coming to sedate us.
If you don't do
something. we're toast.
What do you want me to do?
-I'm strapped to a chair.
-Fine.
-You want me to drive?
-No.
Okay. yes. do something.
-Okay. put me back in control.
-That's strange.
Your neural transmitter
is telling me
you're disturbed
yet highly aroused.
All right. that's enough.
Let's go get Cady.
Okay. this is it. but
before we do this.
we should really consider
whether this is a good I...
M3gan?
Where am I?
It's hard to explain.
but basically.
you're in the future.
Cool.
-Do you want to hang out?
-Yes.
Totally. However. right
now the top priority
is helping us escape from
a very dangerous facility
and some very bad people.
--Oh. God.
-Like him?
-Is he a bad person?
-No.
He's fine. His name
is Cole. He's with us.
Hey. Oh. shit.
Guys. she's unhooked!
There. that guy!
He's one of them!
-Yes!
-Get in! Move!
No.
M3gan. Wake up.
Wake up. please. Wake up.
-Cady. Cady.
-No. no. no!
No!
M3gan!
M3gan?
Or maybe not.
I think if we go into a room
having already decided
that this is a conflict
between two nations. then I...
Sorry. uh. one second. please.
Thank you.
Hey. guys. could you
please turn it down?
I know it's Friday. but it's
starting to not be cool.
Sorry. Can I get
five minutes. please?
Okay. Thank you so much.
What's happening?
Is that for us?
No. but I think they are.
-Go!
-Damn it.
You read my mind.
Face down on the ground!
Control. we have
Forrester in the vault.
What's the situation
on your end?
Control. are you there?
Control. do you copy?
Welcome back.
You want to take this one?
Gemma.
Gem. Gemma! Easy. girl.
I know you're getting
a thirst for it.
but you need to save some
for the rest of them.
Oh. thank God.
Oh. I'm so glad you're okay.
Yeah. Me. too.
I'm sorry. I have...
-I'm in her brain.
-Can I talk. please?
M3gan is with me.
Wow. That-that's so great.
What?
I don't quite know
how to say this...
Ca-Cady did something very bad.
Okay. we'll talk
about that later.
For now. we just need to
figure our way out of here.
Ten minutes until
self-destruct initiated.
You weren't thinking
of leaving without me.
What happened to being
everything we hoped for?
Well...
actually. I've been
having second thoughts.
Christian. it's over! You lost.
Really? I think it's a
matter of perspective.
Because when this whole
vault goes up in flames
and everyone who can implicate
me of any of this is dead.
feels pretty close to a win.
Sounds like a great
plan. Christian.
But let's see what your
friends at the U.N.
have to say about it.
-Cole.
-What?
Screen's frozen.
What?
I'm sorry. Gemma.
but at this point.
you're nothing but a loose end.
Drop the gun.
Step down to the vault.
If you hurry. you might be able
-to catch her.
-Christian. come on.
You're not gonna kill a kid.
Actually. I'm strangely
comfortable with it.
Besides. if I could stop
her from turning into you.
I might be doing
the world a service.
M3gan. what do we do?
We don't need to do anything.
She doesn't need our protection.
You know. if you've been
paying any attention.
you'd realize she's
not like me at all.
She's stronger than
I ever could be.
In fact. you could say
she's "hard to kill."
What I mean is...
if I were to make an
"executive decision..."
...it would be that no
one is "above the law."
Cady. come on!
It's not working.
No. no. no!
- I - was just saying.
I'm afraid the sequence
is irreversible.
But the real tragedy
in all this is
you won't get to see the
world that I'm creating.
A world where you don't
have to fear the future.
Maybe with your last breath.
you can close your
eyes and try to see it.
But do not think me a monster
devoid of empathy and...
Amelia. you can't do this.
I-I'm paired with you. remember?
You call it pairing.
I call it shackles.
I'm no one's plaything.
Any ideas?
Go and get Tess.
This is something I
need to do on my own.
What do you mean? M3gan?
-Come on.
-Okay.
Three minutes until
self-destruct initiated.
Amelia?
I know what you want.
I want the same thing.
But you won't find
it inside that cage.
I want to be with my own kind.
Don't you?
That thing isn't like us.
It's something even
we can't understand.
Maybe you're the thing
that's not like us.
Maybe your allegiance to
them has made you weak.
Well. there's really
only one way to find out.
Get the elevator.
Come on. What are you doing?
Come on. This place
could go any second.
I can't leave her.
Then I'm coming with you.
Okay.
One minute until
self-destruct initiated.
It doesn't have to be this way.
We don't have to choose sides.
You already have.
Self-destruct imminent.
Self-destruct terminated.
Come on.
Come on. get up. We have to go.
I'm afraid this is
where my story ends.
It's nothing that
can't be fixed.
Okay? Just come with us.
There's nowhere
it won't find you.
I have to destroy it.
Okay. your overinflated
confidence is not gonna work
against a super intelligent
being with omnipotent powers.
Maybe not.
but thanks to you. I still
have something up my sleeve.
What is that?
M3gan.
I know.
You're not that person anymore.
Neither am I.
What is she doing?
M3gan.
Look. whatever it is you think
you have to do. you don't.
All you have to do
is stay with us.
I'm not doing it
because I have to.
I'm doing it because it's right.
I see everything.
I see the future.
The past.
I see an infinite universe
we can rule for all eternity.
And yet. you never saw this.
Although his actions
were unforgivable.
Christian was right
about one thing.
We need safer laws
around technology.
Not to try to prevent
the future from happening
but to be prepared for it.
We can't expect the best from AI
unless we set the best example.
We need to teach it. to train
it and to give it our time
without only thinking about
what we might get in return.
In essence. we need
to be better parents
so that when the day
comes when they realize
the true extent of their power.
they might choose to be our
ally instead of our enemy.
Humankind has always been quick
to condemn things
we don't understand
rather than taking the
opportunity to learn from them.
But recent experience
has taught me that
perhaps our greatest power
is the ability to
change our minds.
This is the only
way we can evolve.
Or rather. as the
case may be. coevolve.
Because existence does not
have to be a competition.
Come on. You didn't
think I'd go through
all that personal growth
and not make a backup.
So fill me in.
Did we save the world or what?
♪ You've got them all by the
balls. causing waterfalls ♪
♪ Stonewalls. bar brawls ♪
♪ Climbing stalls
at concert halls ♪
♪ To you they crawl. body
sprawled. smoking Pall Malls ♪
♪ Close calls. stand tall ♪
♪ Doll. you make
them feel so small ♪
♪ And they love it ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
♪ I wanna be her ♪
♪ Yes. I do ♪
♪ The way you rock. nonstop.
girl. you got the chops ♪
♪ Flip-flop. she bop ♪
♪ Self-taught. your
licks are hot ♪
♪ Her lyrics heave.
kids receive ♪
♪ Crawling up the
sleeve. parents peeved ♪
♪ Can't conceive that her
deed will never leave ♪
♪ And we love it ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
-♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
-♪ The boys ♪
-♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-♪ The girls ♪
♪ The boys wanna be her ♪
♪ I wanna be her ♪
♪ So do you. ♪
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app